Register of the Lillian Mae MacRae Papers, 1916-1917
Hoover Institution Archives
Lillian Mae MacRae Papers,
1916-1917
58001
MacRae, Lillian Mae
1 folder (0.1 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence and postcards, relating to the collection of funds in California for relief work in Belgium and northern France.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Access Points
International relief.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1914-1918--Civilian relief.; World War, 1914-1918--California.; World War, 1914-1918--United States.; California.; United States--Foreign relations.
Container List
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - Block, Gab, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - April 26
    - May 22
    - June 5
    - July 2
    - July 30
  - Herlinden, F. (?), 1916 July 21
  - Fuller, Loie
    - Undated
    - 1916 May 12
    - 1917 January 24
  - 1917 February 6 (P.S. to above letter)
  - Rancougue, Vtesse de, ? August 8
  - Steen, Comtesse van den, 1918 January 22
- PICTURES AND CLIPPINGS
  - Clippings from the Washington press, Niles, Calif. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Story and picture of Loie Fuller and "some of the girls"
  - Postal cards
    - Pictures of Loie Fuller
    - Pictures of Loie Fuller and group
    - Picture of Loie Fuller in Red Cross uniform
    - Picture of Maria, 1916-19
    - Picture of Maria and child
    - Picture of bust of Auguste Rodin
    - Picture of Royal Family of Belgium
    - Picture of Elizabeth of Belgium and son
    - Picture of Queen of Belgium
  - Calling card of Mrs. James Ray Whipple